Hi.
In this lesson, give a learn how to manage the charts in chart GPT.
We will go through everything you can do, how to create new charts, how to use temporary
charts, how to rename, delete, archive chart, and of course, how to share charts with your
colleagues and friends using a simple link.
So, let's get started.
When you just open chart GPT, you will see this empty screen with ability to type a message,
you can just click on new chart to see this screen.
What is important to know is that each new chart is like a fresh page.
GPT doesn't remember anything from your previous chart, or if you have two charts and
you'll share something in one chart, then another chart doesn't know about it.
Let me show you.
Again, let's add a sum, any of you start new chart, do I like, Lego?
I don't know if you like Lego, you haven't mentioned it yet.
You see it's different chart, it doesn't move it.
And if I ask in this chart, same, that's like Lego, the correct way is say, do I am asking
you, oh god, yeah, you are asking me if I like it, since you told me others that I like
Lego, the answer is yes, so you can see that he remembers the history within the one
chart, within the current chart.
Okay, now let's talk about temporary charts.
To create temporary charts, create new chart and click on this icon, so sometimes you
want to just ask Thompson, quick and private and don't want to save it in the history.
That's when temporary chart is useful.
Temporary chart works only when it's open and once it closes chart, everything is gone.
This doesn't, tragically doesn't store it.
So, change it, if forget the conversations completely and it's great for one time question,
some sensitive code examples or other sensitive information.
As you can see right here, so my state copy of the temporary chart within 30 days, I guess
for some safe purpose, but it won't be available right here.
Okay, if I ask Thompson, so, word is the difference between a yard and an angular, for example,
he's answering, but if I switch to, so you see the chart won't appear here and if I
switch and then I can't go to any other chart, so as you see, this chart is not appearing
in history.
This is how temporary chart works.
Okay, now let's talk about renaming.
Tachyptia automatically gives your chart name based on your context, what you're talking,
what you're discussing in the chart, and if you'd like to rename it, you can click
three dots and click rename, and you can like, I like, let go.
And this is a new chart name.
Okay, so, it can help you much faster recognize which chart, or you can also use a more
decent chart, if you like.
Okay, let's talk now about deleting a chart.
If the chart is no longer useful for you, you can delete it, or you can just always start
the temporary chart, so it won't save it, this is one of the purpose, but if you'd like
to delete chart, you can click also three dots and click delete, you can see, click on
the confirmation, I click delete, it's gone, okay, but if you want to delete everything
of the chart, so you can go to the settings, then inside of your settings, you can go
to the data controls, and you can click delete all charts and connect your relationship.
I do it time to time, because I don't want to store a lot of charts, also another option,
you can do, it's archive in a chart, so if you'd like, you can, for example, add like
archives alone, it's discussion chart archive, so it will go on, but if I click settings,
and it go to data controls, archive it's charts, I don't see if you have one archive
it's chart, and I click on a pirate, or delete it, completely, okay, also I can archive
all charts, if for the reason I want to store them, but just in season, in a chart sidebar,
okay, the another feature is sharing a chart, finally, you can share a chart with others,
so if you click on three dots and click share, so you can see, yeah, give it a lot, you'll
see this chart, you can copy a link, and if I open it in going at the top, you'll see that
I'm not logged in the user, and I can't read this chart, so we can share it with friends,
with colleagues, with anyone else, so it creates public link that shows your conversation,
but has any personal data, might be here, this is perfect, when you did a fix of the bar
host, have some explanation, you can share it with some people, okay, I hope this information
about charts was useful to you, and see you in the next awesome!